{
    "subject": "resource/Balwant_Singh_(footballer)",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Punjab,_India",
    "human_readable": "Balwant Singh (footballer) was born in Punjab, India.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9503907561302185,
            "question": "Is Balwant Singh an Indian footballer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9169452786445618,
            "question": "Name the birthplace of Balwant Singh."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9156940579414368,
            "question": "In which country was Balwant Singh born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8903759121894836,
            "question": "Where was Balwant Singh born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8309051990509033,
            "question": "Is Balwant Singh a famous footballer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8070310354232788,
            "question": "What nationality is Balwant Singh?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8003492951393127,
            "question": "What state in India is Balwant Singh from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6678062677383423,
            "question": "Where did Balwant Singh's football career begin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6438805460929871,
            "question": "What sport is Balwant Singh known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3277154266834259,
            "question": "Is Punjab a state in India?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Balwant Singh (footballer) was born in Punjab, India.",
            "html": "dbpedia_449_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What sport is Balwant Singh known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_449_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Balwant Singh's football career begin?",
            "html": "dbpedia_449_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What state in India is Balwant Singh from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_449_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_449_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_449_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_449_123.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_449_132.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_449_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_449_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_449_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_449_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_449_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_449_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about multiple individuals named Balwant Singh, including his place of birth. Specifically, the document states that \"Balwant Singh (born 15 December 1986) is an Indian professional footballer who plays as a forward for both the club ATK and the Indian national team.\" It also mentions that he was born in Hoshiarpur, Punjab, India, which supports the statement that Balwant Singh (footballer) was born in Punjab, India."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}